https://bodymindintegration.com/home/privacy-policy/

Privacy policy | International Institute for Bodymind Integration
Home
The institute
The IBI institute in Belgium
Why Bodymind Integration?
Pelvic-Heart Integration training
Somatic Centering (Advanced training)
The IBI institute in Belgium
Why Bodymind Integration?
Pelvic-Heart Integration training
Somatic Centering (Advanced training)
1. Management of personal data
In Europe, personal data is notably protected by European regulation 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of April 27, 2016 (entered into force on May 25, 2018) relating to the protection of individuals with regard to data processing personal data and the free movement of such data (GDPR).
When using the bodymindintegration.com site, the following may be collected: the URL of the links through which the user has accessed the bodymindintegration.com site, the user’s access provider, the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the user for purely statistical and anonymous purposes.
In any event, the International Institute for Bodymind Integration (IBI) collects personal information relating to the user only for the need of certain services offered by the bodymindintegration.com site. The user provides this information with full knowledge of the facts, especially when he enters it himself.
Users of the bodymindintegration.com site are therefore informed whether or not they are required to provide this information.
Contact and registration forms:
The information collected on the contact and registration forms of the bodymindintegration.com website is sent by e-mail to respond to requests from internet users relating to IBI services. This information is sent by the https protocol under an SSL certificate allowing the information to be protected when it is sent. They are kept for 1 year and are intended only for IBI.
These data are as follows:
Last name
First name
E-mail adress
Phone
Address, postal code, city, country
Free message in which other personal data could be entered by the user
The data provided is only stored in the IBI mailbox, in an Excel file on Dirk Marivoet’s computer and in the database of the bodymindintegration.com website. The devices where this data is accessible (mobile phones and computers) are protected by a password.
In any case, the user can refuse to provide his personal data. In this case, he will not be able to use the services of the site, nor to request information on these services.
In accordance with the “IT and liberties” law, all users have the right to access, rectify and oppose personal data concerning them by contacting the IBI by email at info@bodymindintegration.com.
No personal information of the user of the bodymindintegration.com site is published without the user’s knowledge, exchanged, transferred, assigned or sold on any medium to third parties.
Hypertext links
The bodymindintegration.com site contains a number of hypertext links to other sites, set up with the authorization of Dirk Marivoet. However, Dirk Marivoet does not have the possibility to check the content of the sites thus visited, and will therefore assume no responsibility for this fact. In the event that a user or visitor wishes to set up a hyperlink to the bodymindintegration.com site, it will be their responsibility to send an email accessible on the site in order to formulate their request for the establishment of a hyperlink. Dirk Marivoet reserves the right to accept or refuse a hyperlink without having to justify its decision.
Cookies
Browsing the bodymindintegration.com site may cause the installation of cookie (s) on the user’s computer, smartphone or tablet. A cookie is a small file, which does not allow the identification of the user, but which records information relating to the navigation of a device on a site.
We thus automatically collect certain information about you when you simply browse our website, including: information about the use of our site, such as the areas you visit and the services you access, your IP address, the type of your browser, your access times.
Such information is used exclusively for internal statistics and security of the bodymindintegration.com site, or to improve the quality of the services offered to you.
The bodymindintegration.com site uses third-party company solutions that require the use of cookies that collect personal information:
Google Analytics statistical solution.
Security solution Ithemes Security
Refusal to install a cookie may make it impossible to access certain services. The user can however configure his computer in the following way, to refuse the installation of cookies:
In Internet Explorer: tool tab (cog-shaped pictogram at the top right) / internet options. Click on Confidentiality and choose Block all cookies. Validate on Ok.
In Firefox: at the top of the browser window, click the Firefox button, then go to the Options tab. Click on the Privacy tab. Set the Storage rules on: use the custom settings for history. Finally uncheck it to deactivate cookies.
In Safari: Click at the top right of the browser on the menu pictogram (symbolized by a cog). Select Settings. Click on Show advanced settings. In the “Confidentiality” section, click on Content settings. In the “Cookies” section, you can block cookies.
In Chrome: Click at the top right of the browser on the menu pictogram (symbolized by three horizontal lines). Select Settings. Click on Show advanced settings. In the “Confidentiality” section, click on preferences. In the “Confidentiality” tab, you can block cookies.
Applicable law and attribution of jurisdiction
Any dispute in connection with the use of the bodymindintegration.com site is subject to Belgian law.
The consumer customer has the option of submitting a request for amicable resolution by mediation, within a period of less than one year from his written complaint to the professional.
International Institute for Bodymind Integration
Destelbergenstraat 49-51 9040 Ghent, Belgium
+32 9 228 49 11
info@bodymindintegration.com
Facebook
Twitter
Linkedin
Write us an email
Privacy policy
Legal Notice
Sitemap
Design by Adaracom
This website uses cookies to improve your experience, especially through the Google Analytics service. We don't use cookies for commercial use and all information gathered are anonymous. OKPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Privacy Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
